http://www.vectra-corp.com/privacy-policy

Privacy PolicyGeneral Privacy InformationVectra Corporation respects the privacy of our customers, business partners and employees. We recognise the need for appropriate protections and management of your personal information that you provide to us. Vectra Corporation has therefore established this Privacy Statement to assist in understanding what information we collect and how that information is used.Personal InformationPersonal Information is information that can be used to identify or contact a specific individual, such as a name, address, telephone number or email address. Vectra Corporation may collect certain personal information from customers, business partners, employees and candidates for employment. Vectra Corporation does not collect personal information unless you choose to provide such personal information during the process of ordering products or services, requesting information, subscribing to the support extranet. The types of personal information you provide to us on these pages may include name, address, phone number, e-mail address, user IDs and passwords, billing and transaction information, credit card or other financial information, contact preferences, educational and employment background, job interest data and benefit choices.Vectra Corporation will use personal information to provide customers with information and services to help us better understand your needs and requirements. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction or order, scope a project to communicate with you, to deliver products/services to you, to bill you for products/services you purchased, and to provide ongoing service and support. In addition, any information provided as part of a transaction may be used to determine your liability against Australian GST requirements. Occasionally we may use your information to contact you to complete surveys that we use for marketing and quality assurance purposes.Vectra Corporations’ policies regarding the use of personal information in email are in compliance with the U.S. and E.U. SPAM laws. In Australia, we are bound by the Mandatory Breach Reporting and Privacy Act, and associated guidelines for technical controls published by the Office of Information Commissioner as well as other applicable laws and codes affecting your personal information.Vectra Corporation may contract and engage with third party service providers and suppliers to deliver products, services and customer solutions. Vectra Corporation may share personal information with its service providers and suppliers for the sole purpose and only to the extent needed to support the customers’ business needs. Service providers and suppliers are required to keep confidential the personal information received from Vectra Corporation and may not use it for any purpose other than as originally intended.Third parties receiving personal information from Vectra Corporation are expected to apply the same level of privacy protection as contained in this Privacy Statement.Except as provided above, Vectra Corporation will not share personal information with any other third parties without your permission, unless required by, or in connection with, law enforcement action, subpoena or other litigation, or applicable law.Vectra Corporation will not sell, trade or lease your personal information to others.Vectra Corporation does not request or receive personal information specifying medical or health conditions, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, or information specifying the sex life of the individual.Vectra Corporation strives to keep your personal information accurate and provides the opportunity to change your information where possible. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as a password and user ID, before granting access to your data.Vectra Corporation will not process personal information in a way that is incompatible with the purposes for which it has been collected or subsequently authorised by the individual, as required by applicable law. Vectra Corporation is committed to taking all efforts to secure the personal data you choose to provide us.Vectra Corporation collects and/or logs Internet Protocol addresses, Internet domain names, the web browser and operating system used to access the Vectra Corporation web site, the files visited, the time spent in each file, and the time and date of each visit. Vectra Corporation also uses cookies on its web sites. Cookies are identifiers that can be sent from a web site via your browser to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Thereafter when you visit a web site, a message is sent back to the web server by the browser accessing the web site. You may elect not to accept cookies by changing the designated settings on your web browser. However, not utilising cookies may prevent you from using certain functions and features of web sites. The information collected from the use of cookies is used and analysed to improve Vectra Corporations’ web sites. Vectra Corporation may utilise the services of a third party vendor to assist in the collection and processing of the aforementioned web browsing information.If you have any questions or would like further information about our privacy and information handling practices, please contact us: privacy.officer@vectra-corp.comContact VectraFill out the form and we’ll be in touch as soon as possible or call our team on 1800 816 044.Contact Us - Popup
Country
Afghanistan Aland Islands Albania Algeria American Samoa Andorra Angola Anguilla Antarctica Antigua and Barbuda Argentina Armenia Aruba Australia Austria Azerbaijan Bahamas Bahrain Bangladesh Barbados Belarus Belgium Belize Benin Bermuda Bhutan Bolivia Bosnia and Herzegovina Botswana Bouvet Island Brazil Brunei Bulgaria Burkina Faso Burundi Cambodia Cameroon Canada Cape Verde Cayman Islands Central African Republic Chad Chile China Colombia Comoros Congo Costa Rica Côte d'Ivoire Croatia Cuba Curacao Cyprus Czech Republic Denmark Djibouti Dominica Dominican Republic East Timor Ecuador Egypt El Salvador Equatorial Guinea Eritrea Estonia Ethiopia Fiji Finland France French Guiana French Polynesia Gabon Gambia Georgia Germany Ghana Gibraltar Greece Greenland Grenada Guadeloupe Guam Guatemala Guernsey Guinea Guinea-Bissau Guyana Haiti Honduras Hong Kong Hungary Iceland India Indonesia Iran Iraq Ireland Israel Italy Jamaica Japan Jersey Jordan Kazakhstan Kenya Kiribati North Korea South Korea Kosovo Kuwait Kyrgyzstan Laos Latvia Lebanon Lesotho Liberia Libya Liechtenstein Lithuania Luxembourg Macao Macedonia Madagascar Malawi Malaysia Maldives Mali Malta Marshall Islands Martinique Mauritania Mauritius Mayotte Mexico Micronesia Moldova Monaco Mongolia Montenegro Montserrat Morocco Mozambique Myanmar Namibia Nauru Nepal Netherlands New Caledonia New Zealand Nicaragua Niger Nigeria Norway Northern Mariana Islands Oman Pakistan Palau Palestine Panama Papua New Guinea Paraguay Peru Philippines Pitcairn Poland Portugal Puerto Rico Qatar Romania Russia Rwanda Saint Kitts and Nevis Saint Lucia Saint Vincent and the Grenadines Samoa San Marino Sao Tome and Principe Saudi Arabia Senegal Serbia and Montenegro Seychelles Sierra Leone Singapore Slovakia Slovenia Solomon Islands Somalia South Africa South Sudan Spain Sri Lanka Sudan Suriname Swaziland Sweden Switzerland Syria Taiwan Tajikistan Tanzania Thailand Togo Tonga Trinidad and Tobago Tunisia Turkey Turkmenistan Tuvalu Uganda Ukraine United Arab Emirates United Kingdom United States Uruguay Uzbekistan Vanuatu Vatican City Venezuela Vietnam Virgin Islands, British Virgin Islands, U.S. Yemen Zambia Zimbabwe
Submit
If you are human, leave this field blank.
Banking & FinanceAirlinesMajor RetailersHealthService ProvidersGovernmentInsuranceMedia & Entertainment TOPContact usContact Vectra
× Complete the form below to send an enquiry to the Vectra team and we will respond within 48 hours.Contact Us - Footer
Country
Afghanistan Aland Islands Albania Algeria American Samoa Andorra Angola Anguilla Antarctica Antigua and Barbuda Argentina Armenia Aruba Australia Austria Azerbaijan Bahamas Bahrain Bangladesh Barbados Belarus Belgium Belize Benin Bermuda Bhutan Bolivia Bosnia and Herzegovina Botswana Bouvet Island Brazil Brunei Bulgaria Burkina Faso Burundi Cambodia Cameroon Canada Cape Verde Cayman Islands Central African Republic Chad Chile China Colombia Comoros Congo Costa Rica Côte d'Ivoire Croatia Cuba Curacao Cyprus Czech Republic Denmark Djibouti Dominica Dominican Republic East Timor Ecuador Egypt El Salvador Equatorial Guinea Eritrea Estonia Ethiopia Fiji Finland France French Guiana French Polynesia Gabon Gambia Georgia Germany Ghana Gibraltar Greece Greenland Grenada Guadeloupe Guam Guatemala Guernsey Guinea Guinea-Bissau Guyana Haiti Honduras Hong Kong Hungary Iceland India Indonesia Iran Iraq Ireland Israel Italy Jamaica Japan Jersey Jordan Kazakhstan Kenya Kiribati North Korea South Korea Kosovo Kuwait Kyrgyzstan Laos Latvia Lebanon Lesotho Liberia Libya Liechtenstein Lithuania Luxembourg Macao Macedonia Madagascar Malawi Malaysia Maldives Mali Malta Marshall Islands Martinique Mauritania Mauritius Mayotte Mexico Micronesia Moldova Monaco Mongolia Montenegro Montserrat Morocco Mozambique Myanmar Namibia Nauru Nepal Netherlands New Caledonia New Zealand Nicaragua Niger Nigeria Norway Northern Mariana Islands Oman Pakistan Palau Palestine Panama Papua New Guinea Paraguay Peru Philippines Pitcairn Poland Portugal Puerto Rico Qatar Romania Russia Rwanda Saint Kitts and Nevis Saint Lucia Saint Vincent and the Grenadines Samoa San Marino Sao Tome and Principe Saudi Arabia Senegal Serbia and Montenegro Seychelles Sierra Leone Singapore Slovakia Slovenia Solomon Islands Somalia South Africa South Sudan Spain Sri Lanka Sudan Suriname Swaziland Sweden Switzerland Syria Taiwan Tajikistan Tanzania Thailand Togo Tonga Trinidad and Tobago Tunisia Turkey Turkmenistan Tuvalu Uganda Ukraine United Arab Emirates United Kingdom United States Uruguay Uzbekistan Vanuatu Vatican City Venezuela Vietnam Virgin Islands, British Virgin Islands, U.S. Yemen Zambia Zimbabwe
Submit
If you are human, leave this field blank.
